I am a Front End Developer and consultant based in Oklahoma City. As a developer, my primary focus is design, experience, and user interaction with a continued drive to learn new frameworks and languages. I am a published Paranormal Historian specializing in the Victorian Era. I am a passionate creative-type with a deep love for programming.

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JS (React, Node.js) HTML/CSS/Bootstrap SQL

## **PORTFOLIO**

junebrown.journoportfolio.com github.com/june-brown

### **EDUCATION**

OK Coders Bootcamp Web Development (HTML/CSS, JS, Node.js)

OCCC

History, Museum Studies

**UAFS** 

General Studies, Pathology

# June Brown Front End Developer

405.549.9952 rebekahj.b@outlook.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# CLIENT SUCCESS SPECIALIST CLEVYR

JANUARY 2020- MARCH 2020

Worked as a liaison between clients and developers to facilitate client needs, sprint work, and information. Wrote articles based on business to business, development, and various other areas. Contributed to writing copy and developing marketing for game apps.

## CREATIVE DIRECTOR, FRONT END DEVELOPER DEEP FORK TECHNOLOGY

SEPTEMBER 2019 - DECEMBER 2019

Multiple roles of responsibility to support the team - project management, marketing, creative director, and front end developer. Responsible for mentorship of Junior Developer Intern and overseeing website creation for various clients from consult to mockup to implementation and launch. Developing procedures for general project management software and project implementation. Develop marketing materials for print and company website.

#### TECHNICAL AND BUSINESS WRITER, FREELANCER

JANUARY 2012 - DECEMBER 2019

Provide a wide range of writing services and expertise to various clients, businesses, publications, and websites, including: resumes and cover letters, articles, training material, writing prompts, how-to articles, press releases, contracts, technical reports, and web content. Conducted research for the purpose of identifying trends and current industry developments that could be used to update and improve the current level of technical content for various clients.

# LEGAL ASSISTANT, TECHNICAL WRITER KEMPER

**APRIL 2017 - OCTOBER 2018** 

Provided a range of paraprofessional and administrative support services to the Legal Department's litigation office by preparing both routine and specialized legal documents and correspondence and oversaw the day to day operations and support activities. Assisted in contract preparation, completion, and administration, screened requests for legal action or information, providing referrals to other counsel or notification to Legal Department management as appropriate.